你想要哪一個呀?
Which one are you going for,bud?
白色的那個?戴眼罩的?
The white one? With goggles?
我來告訴怎麼把它吊上來,好嗎?
Okay,I'm gonna show you how to get there. Okay?
開始,你要沿著...
Okay,you're gonna follow
這條線,一直移動...
this line till it gets to...
直到它進入這個圈,明白嗎?
Till it gets to this circle,okay?
當它碰到圈了,按下按鈕.
When it hits that circle,you press the button.
然後,然後沿著這條線
Then you're gonna follow this bottom line
直到它到達這個圈
until it gets to this circle.
按一下按鈕,好嗎?明白了嗎?
Then you press the button,okay? Got it?
你還有錢麼?
Okay,you got any money?
好吧,這裏是1元
Okay,well,here's $1.
祝你好運
Good luck.
《信號》
你好
嗨
你激動嗎
嘿
Hey.
Nomad回來了
Nomad's back.
他又來找我們麻煩了
He's messing with us again.
他說了什麼?
What did he say?
"你非法黑進MIT的服務器"
"Your hack into MIT servers was legit."
回復好快
That was fast.
"啦啦啦..你激動了"
啦啦啦....這是什麼?
"Ta,ta,ta." What is that?
"他們以為是我們幹的..
"They put that shit on us.
我們差點被開除."
"We almost got expelled."
"MIT比娃娃還幼稚.你來找我,我欠你的.
vibes"
Vibes
"Vibes."
Vibes是誰
Who's this Vibes?
好吧,帥哥
Okay,guy.
"我們要在DEFCON上曝光你
"We're going to expose you at DEF CON,
所以你最好小心點."
"so you better watch your back."
嘿,這是什麼?
Dude,what is that?
什麼...
What the...
到裏面去.
Go into the building.
去拿Pwnie
(Pwnie Express 網絡監測設備公司
由美國"國防先進研究項目局DARPA"支持,參與開發黑客設備)
Get the Pwnie.
好吧,我們開工
All right,let's do this.
打開一個Linux終端並啟動Nmap
Open up a Linux terminal and start an Nmap,dude
Haley和我明天還要開車
Haley's gonna have to drive tomorrow.
嘿,集中注意力
Hey,focus.
這就是我要說的,我沒辦法集中注意力
That's what I'm saying,I won't be able to.
從技術上講,她一直在移動
Technically she's the one moving,
所以從技術上,她應該在開車
so technically she should be driving.
你打開了嗎?
Is it open yet?
等幾秒
In a sec.
好了,我這邊好了
Okay,I'm good. Okay.
隨便輸入點什麼
Okay,type something.
讓我編個笑話
I'm trying to think of something funny.
該死的
Damn.
"安卓系統被黑是遲早問題"
"Do androids take an electric sheet?"
你個二貨
You're stupid.
好吧,我拿到了C&C服務器的IP地址.
Okay,read me out the IPs on the C&C servers.
"192.236.19.147"
"192. 236. 19. 147."
147開始嗅探連接.
147. Start sniffing connections.
收到,跟蹤竊聽中..
Copy that. Firing up the listeners.
好吧,這傢伙的Toast代碼
All right,this guy's toast.
內華達州
Nevada.
老兄,我們正好要經過內華達州
Dude,we're going right through Nevada.
-我們抓到他了 -我們抓到他了
We got him. We got him!
你們非要這時間鬧嗎?
Are you guys being serious right now?
你明天早上開車,所以
Well,you're driving in the morning,
晚安
so good night.
我要來抓你了,麻省理工學院的叛徒
I'd like to see you make me,you Caltech turncoat.
Haley,這個魚缸正在漏什麼東西出來
Haley,this fish tank's leaking something.
那是水,Jonah
It's water,Jonah.
-好噁心 -閉嘴
It's gross. Shut up.
你,麻省理工的叛徒
You Caltech turncoats.
老兄,你能先不說這事嗎?
Dude,can you stop saying that?
這裏的信號好爛
Signal sucks out here.
信號確實不好
You're right,it does suck.
-嘿,來一顆炫邁嗎? -不了,謝謝
Hey,you want one of these? No,I'm good,thanks.
你要來一點嗎?
You want?
兄弟
Dude.
-什麼? -來看看這個
What? Check this out.
什麼鬼東西?
What the hell?
他是怎麼搞到的?
Why isn't that working?
那是我的車嗎?
Is that my car?
沒錯,交通攝像頭拍的
Yeah. It's a traffic camera.
這傢伙好牛X
This guy is so gnarly.
他怎麼有我的車的照片?
How does he have a picture of my car?
等一下
Hold on a sec.
為什麼這傢伙不怕麻煩去黑掉MIT
Why would this guy go to all the trouble to hack into MIT,
然後,還這樣來嘲諷我們?
and then,you know,just taunt us like this?
任何人都有可能有任何理由,比如
The same reason anyone does anything. Acknowledgment.
"爭強好勝"什麼的
"I'm better than you,you're better than me," whatever.
拿著,我不能解鎖.你試試
Here,dude,I can't unlock it. You try.
你們應該停止挑釁他
You guys should just stop provoking him.
他可能只是一個小孩子.
He's probably just some little kid.
Nick,我們還去不去抓他?
Nick,are we doing this or not?
我做不到,兄弟
I can't,dude.
你什麼意思,你不能?
What do you mean,you can't?
現在不行
I just can't right now.
你看,我也知道我們要送Haley去加利福尼亞
Look,I get we have to take Haley to California.
但是,沒有理由我們不去抓他
But there's no reason we shouldn't do this,too.
黑MIT是一件事,但是黑Haley的電腦?你還能忍?
Nomad hacking into MIT is one thing,but Haley's computer?
這傢伙還會再做更瘋狂的事
No,but it's crazy not to go after this guy.
-Jonah,看下多少錢?  -我們就快抓到他了
Jonah,what's the sales tax? We're so close.
6.3
6.3.
它在路上.
It's on the way.
14.74,不用找了.
$14.74. You can keep the change.
你們要喝點什麼嗎?
You guys want something?
要的
Yeah.
-咖啡? -是的,我喜歡喝咖啡.
Coffee? Yeah,I'd love a coffee.
-黑咖啡嗎?  -我幫你拿
Black? There you go.
是的,謝謝
Yeah,please.
啥事?
What?
Nick有跟你說過關於我要搬走的事嗎?
Has Nick said anything to you about me moving?
沒有
No.
什麼都沒說?
Nothing?
沒說,顯然他覺得你會玩消失一年.
No,obviously he's bummed you're gonna be gone for a year.
這似乎只是他試圖
It just seems like he's trying to
讓自己疏遠我,你明白嗎?
distance himself from me,you know?
你看,你們是我最好的朋友,
Look,you guys are my best friends,
而我只是...
and I'm just...
我不想摻和你們的問題
I'm the wrongest guy to ask.
懂了
Yeah.
我擦
Oh,crap.
嘿...
Hey.
你沒事吧,兄弟?
You all right,bud?
-我很好 -是嗎?
I'm fine. Yeah?
我沒事,我沒事.
I'm fine,I'm fine.
我再去買點咖啡
I'm gonna get more coffees.
我....去動車
I'm gonna move the car.
好朋友
Best friends!
這杯滿了
Is this one mine?
恩
Yeah.
我再倒第二杯
I already put two in.
我搞的定
I got it.
Nick,我幫你並不是認為你需要我幫忙
Nick,I offer to help not because I think you need it,
我知道你自己能行
but because I know you don't.
是啊,你們不用為我擔心,好嗎?
Yeah,well,you won't have to worry about that soon,will you?
好吧
Okay.
謝了兄弟
Thanks,bud.
我們離那傢伙不遠,是嗎?
We're not really that far from this guy,are we?
180英里,你想抓他嗎?
180 miles,give or take.
好吧,兄弟,我們去抓他
All right,dude,let's do it.
我們走
Let's go.
這才是我愛的那個Nickholas Eastman
Now,see,this is the Nickholas Eastman I love.
自信,果斷,有競爭力
You know,just determined,ruthless,competitive.
就像咖啡因上腦了
Oh,and favors caffeine.
Haley去哪裏了?
Where's Haley?
我不知道,我記得她去..呃......
I don't know. I think she walked,uh...
那邊了
That way.
Haley,我很抱歉,我一直心不在焉.
Haley,look,I'm sorry. It's just,I've been distracted.
我覺得你準備做一件大事
I think you're getting ready to make a big speech.
我覺得這整個行程,
I think this whole trip is about
是你早就準備好的
you getting ready to make it.
你在說什麼?我不想做什麼大事
What are you talking about? I'm not gonna make a speech.
停
Stop.
Haley,你知道我為此付出了多少嗎?
Haley,you know how many times I've played this out in my head?
每周檢查2次身體
Twice-a-week doctor's appointments.
誰知道有多少核磁共振和測試?
Who knows how many MRIs and tests.
最後坐在輪椅上.
Eventually a wheelchair.
想的都是"如果你會跟我分手"
All the time wondering if you're gonna break up with me.
-別說了  -當你厭倦了這種....
Stop. When you're gonna get tired of this bullshit.
這不公平,你讓我覺得我很壞
It's not fair to make me the bad guy without my input.
Haley,這不是我在說什麼.
Haley,that's not what I'm saying.
我只是說我能不能再把你找回來
I'm just saying I'm not gonna be the guy who holds you back.
酷.所以,呃......
Cool. So,uh...
我謹離開了一年
I move away for one year
你最害怕什麼的要發生的事,
and because you're scared of what's gonna happen,
你馬上再打來分手?
you immediately resort to breaking up?
我只是說...
I'm just saying...
我只是說,我需要保護自己.
I'm just saying I need to protect myself.
怕被我傷害?
From what?
這是你的真心話嗎?
Is it your heart talking or your head?
這是實話
It's me talking.
但你總是告訴我
But you're the one that always told me
勇敢去做而不是逃避
to run toward something and not away from it.
是啊,這就是為什麼我這麼恨自己
Yeah,well,that was before all this shit.
你在幹嘛?
What are you doing?
你可以繼續你的承諾,我不要了
You can keep your promises. I don't want them.
Haley
Haley.
你要在這裏左轉
You just take a left up here.
還有20英里左右
It's about 20 miles or so.
也許應該先讓Haley在這裏下車
Maybe we should drop Haley off first.
你能不能別理我,就像我已經下車了?
Can you not talk about me like I'm not in the car?
Haley,你沒必要一起去
Haley,you don't have to come along.
不,我想見一見這個混蛋
No,I wanna meet this asshole.
我也想
Me,too.
繼續開,貌似還有四分之一英里
Just keep going. We still got,like,a quarter mile.
-停,停,我們開過頭了  -什麼?
What?
過頭了,倒回去
Yeah,back up.
還有20~30英尺
Say,20 or 30 feet.
停,停車
Stop,Stop.
-就是這裏 -你確定?
You serious?
就是這裏,沒錯
It's right here. It's right here.
別讓我們困在這裏,Nick
Don't get us stuck. Please,Nick.
放心吧
We're fine.
這是這裏
It's over here.
快吧車燈關了
You should kill the headlights.
你確定要這麼做嗎?
Are you sure you want to do this?
不是我亂說
I'm not gonna lie.
這裏看上去不對勁
This doesn't look right.
你覺得怎樣?
What do you think?
我們坐在車裏是沒用的
We're not gonna know by sitting in the car.
來吧,我們進去,帶上你的相機.
Come on,let's go. Get your camera.
Haley,留在車裏鎖上門,行嗎?
Haley,stay in and lock the doors,okay?
Nick
Nick.
你知道你在干蠢事,對嗎?
You know all this is stupid,right?
你覺得我們找對地方了嗎?
Where do you think we went wrong?
你想說什麼?
What are you talking about?
你懂的,像這麼一個隨機分配的IP地址.
You know,it must have been,like,a random IP allocation.
他可能在世界上任何地方鏈接...
Like,they could be in Georgia for all we know.
比如,歐洲的格魯吉亞
Like,Europe Georgia.
閉嘴
Shut up.
或者,這是他的一個中繼點.
Or they could be using this as a relay point.
一個大媽把那椅子坐壞了
A big mama sat in that chair.
我不得不說,這裏不像有人住
I'm gonna have to say there's nobody here,Nick.
老兄,他不在這裏
Dude,Nomad is not here.
-讓我們再找找  -他不在這裏
Let's take a look. He's not here.
我們就看看,馬上就走
We'll take a look and then we'll go.
讓我們找找看
Let's go find him.
誰會住在這裏?
A hillbilly lives here.
這傢伙有個小孩嗎?
This guy has a baby?
噓!
Shh!
Jonah?
老兄,我看到你了,你在幹嘛?
Dude,I can see you. What are you doing?
嘿!
Hey!
哥們,你真是個混蛋!
Dude,you're such an asshole!
你看到這個搞笑的椅子了嗎?
How funny is this little chair?
它就這麼對著角落放著
It was really facing the corner like this.
來吧.還有一個地下室.
Come on. There's a basement.
你真是個變態
You're such a kike.
下去
Go down.
不去,你下去
Screw that,you go down.
小心點
Be careful.
這是什麼地方?
What is this place?
快來看看吧,夥計.
Check it out,man.
那些是什麼?
What are those?
服務器機架
Server racks.
這就奇怪了
That's weird.
Haley
Oh,wait. Haley!
Haley!Haley!Haley!
Haley! Haley! Haley!
Haley!
我靠,什麼鬼東西?
What the hell?
-那是什麼聲音?  -我不知道.
I don't know.
-為什麼車門都開著?  -我不知道!
Why are the car doors open like that? I don't know!
Haley!
-Haley! -噓!
Haley! Shh!
聽
Listen.
哦.天哪
Oh,my God.
Haley!Haley!
Haley! Haley!
Haley!
你能...說話嗎?
Can you speak?
我在哪裏?
Where am I?
我動不了
I can't move.
你能告訴我你的名字嗎?
Can you tell me your name?
Nickholas Eastman
Nickholas Eastman.
我是呆萌,Damon Wallace博士.
I'm Damon. Dr. Wallace Damon.
我領導著過渡團隊會幫助你的,
I'm heading up the transition team that's going to help you,
我們所有的人會幫助你回想起經歷過什麼.
help all of us understand exactly what you've been through.
你在說什麼呢?
What are you talking about?
你還記得第一次找到那個信號是在哪裏嗎?
Can you recall for me the first time you encountered the signal?
什麼?
The what?
為什麼我不能動?
Why can't I move?
我們出了什麼事?
What happened to us?
由於你現在的病情比較特殊,
Due to the circumstances surrounding your condition,
我恐怕我們的信息是非常有限的.
I'm afraid that our information is extremely limited.
等等,什麼是我的病情?
Wait,what's my condition?
我要告訴你,Nick
What I'm about to tell you,Nick,
可能會讓你感到不安
you may find a bit disturbing.
你與EBE發生了接觸
You have made contact with an E.B.E.
EBE?
E.B.E.?
外星生物實體
Extraterrestrial Biological Entity.
EBE
E.B.E.
我想我和父母談談
I want to talk to my parents.
對不起,那是不可能的
I'm sorry,that's just not possible.
你在說什麼呢?
What are you talking about?
Haley和Jonah在哪裏?
Where's Haley and Jonah?
我們出了什麼事?
What happened to us?
為什麼我坐在輪椅上?
Why am I in a wheelchair?
為什麼...
Why...
為什麼你穿那件衣服?
Why are you wearing that suit?
在我們不能百分之百肯定這麼做安全之前
We're not 100% certain about what we're dealing with here.
被外星來物污染的可能性是非常高的
The possibility for alien contamination is very real.
當你說"外星污染"
When you say
"alien contamination,"
你的意思是微生物污染,就像病毒?
do you mean microbiological contamination,as in foreign?
保持不動.
Hold still.
哦
Oh.
只是流血了
It's just blood.
-隻是流血了
我們今天就到這裏吧
I think we'll stop here for today.
聯繫坐標9-8-47-91-72.
Contact values at 9-8-47-91-72.
12層.我們能獲得當前坐標嗎?
Level 12. Do we know current value?
停下!你能停下來嗎?停止!倒回去
Stop! Will you stop? Stop! Go back!
你能倒回去嗎?
Can you go back?
Haley怎麼了?
What's wrong with Haley?
和我們一樣先進
As advanced as we are,
不可思議,像這樣一個工具,粗的那頭就像支筆
it's amazing that a tool as crude as a pen still has its place.
寫出來了
There we go.
我想和Haley說話
I want to talk to Haley.
拜託了
Please.
恐怕這是不可能的現在.
I'm afraid that's not possible right now.
為什麼?
Why?
她是被照顧的很好,Nick,我向你保證
She's in good hands,Nick,I promise you.
你現在可以為她做的事 就是幫助我們
The best thing you can do for her right now is to help us.
現在,請你好好的協助我好嗎?
Now,will you please try to cooperate with me?
-好 -很好
Okay. Good.
首先我要問你一些簡單的控制問題
First I'm going to ask you some simple control questions.
你有十個腳趾嗎?
Do you have 10 toes?
是的
Yes.
你來自地球嗎?
Are you from Earth?
是的,我是來自地球
Yes,lam from Earth.
好,謝謝你
Good,thank you.
現在,這個信號,你和你的朋友們發現的
Now,this signal that you and your friends were pursuing,
你什麼時候第一次遇到呢?
when did you first encounter it?
-你的是說Nomad? -是的?
You mean Nomad. Yes.
麻省理工學院
MIT.
他黑了我們學校的安全網絡,並破壞了一些重要的服務器
He got into our school's security network and ruined some major servers,
包括我們個人的.
including our personal ones.
Nick,我要你看些東西
Nick,I want you to watch something.
一個大媽把那椅子坐壞了
A big mama sat in that chair.
你絕對抓不到這個黑客的
You definitely weren't pursuing a hacker.
嘿
Hey.
嘿...
-Jonah? -Nick?
-Jonah? -Nick.
-Jonah! -Nick!
我的天哪!Jonah,你在哪裏?
Oh,my God! Jonah,where are you?
我不知道.我被鎖了起來,我在一個房間裏.
I don't know. I'm locked up,I'm in a room.
我也一樣.我在一個上鎖的房間
Me,too. I'm in a locked room,dude.
我們在哪兒?
Where are we?
我聽他們說,我們不是在地面上
I heard them say we're not allowed above ground
因為我們被污染了
because we were contaminated.
Nomad到底是什麼?他們有告訴你嗎?
What the hell was Nomad? What have they told you?
沒說多少
Not much.
我看到了Haley,她還在昏迷什麼的
I saw Haley. She's in a coma or something.
Nick,這裏的人在做一些奇怪的事
Nick,they're doing some weird shit here,man.
我的身體感覺不對
My body doesn't feel right.
Nick,我必須走了
Nick,I gotta go.
什麼?在哪裏?
What? Where?
這個地方是運作像鐘錶一樣精準
This place is run like a clock.
我不能相信你在說實話
I can't believe you're in the vent!
什麼?老兄,我說的都是事實.
What? Dude,I'm not in the vent.
我說的都是事實!Jonah!Jonah!
I'm not in the vent! Jonah! Jonah!
為什麼有個鐘一直停著?
Why don't you have any clocks that work?
鍾一直停著?
Clocks that work?
是的,走廊上有個鐘一直停在 12:30
Yeah.The one in the hallway is stuck at 12:30.
哪個走廊?
Which hallway?
七個窗口後,左轉
Seven windows back. Left turn.
四個窗口 右轉  兩個窗口的右邊
Four windows. Right turn. Two windows on the right.
旁邊的浴室符號顛倒了,那種卡在 12:30
30.
Nick,那只是一個壞掉的鍾
Nick,it's a broken clock.
謝謝你提醒我它壞了
Thank you for bringing it to my attention.
我們可以繼續分辨顏色和形狀了嗎?
Can we please proceed with the shapes and colors?
去你的,這麼做好二
Screw this. This is stupid.
有什麼問題嗎Nick?你分辨不了?
What's the matter,Nick? Can't you do it?
不,我選擇不去分辨
No,I choose not to do it.
選擇?你不想這麼做?
Choose? You choose not to do it?
這聽起來感覺你好傲嬌
That sounds like pride talking.
很傻很天真  是這樣吧
False and foolish pride. That's all.
金字塔 黃色
Pyramid,yellow.
-然後 -正方形 藍色 球 綠色
And the... Cube,blue. Sphere,green.
藍字小瓷磚上的"零",意思是
The blue tile here that says "Zero"
對應於綠色的立方體.
corresponds with the green cube.
這裏的黃磚"六個一",說去與多維數據集.
The yellow tile here that says "Six" goes with the cube.
這裏的綠色瓷磚"五個一",說去與黃色的金字塔.
The green tile here that says "Five" goes with the yellow pyramid.
綠色立方體那張用藍色立方體形狀.
The green cube goes with the blue shaped cube.
黃色書面球體變為與綠色形球體.
The yellow written sphere goes with the green-shaped sphere.
藍色書面金字塔去與黃形金字塔.
The blue written pyramid goes with the yellow-shaped pyramid.
"藍",在綠色的寫入黃色,"黃",
"Blue," written in yellow,"yellow," in green,
對應的可見顏色和形狀,而不是書面文字
correspond the visible colors and shapes rather than the written words
因為光的頻譜質量
because the spectral quality of light
更客觀的,可以這麼說,
is more objective,so to speak,
比這些顏色的書面英語單詞.
than the written English words of those colors.
我知道了
I see.
你知道了?你知道什麼了?
You see? What do you mean,you see?
你,Nick
You,Nick.
我感覺我已經從剛才的測試中
I see you and I think I'm beginning
對你有了更加的瞭解
to understand something more about you.
瞭解了什麼?
Understand what?
顏色,形狀,它們對你的影響
The colors,the shapes,they have an effect on you.
我會說這是一種情緒的效果,不是嗎
I'd say it was an emotional effect,wouldn't you?
我不關心的形狀和顏色
I don't care about the shapes and colors,
這些問題對我沒有任何意義  幹嘛要做這種狗屁測試
they don't mean anything to me. They don't mean shit to me!
你煩死我了,事媽
You're the one that's infuriating me,you quack!
"事媽"
"Quack."
我想見Haley
I wanna see Haley
在見到她之前 我不會再說一個字
and I'm not gonna say another word until you let me see her.
好的,Nick
Okay,Nick.
這上面什麼都沒寫
There's nothing on here.
她處於昏迷中,Nick
She's in a coma,Nick.
我們現在沒有什麼可以為她做的
There's nothing that can be done for her right now.
我保證,只要她醒過來
I promise,as soon as she wakes up,
你會是第一個來看望她的
you'll be the first one to see her.
我們已經盡力而為了
Right now we're doing everything humanly possible.
Nick,這個地方 好詭異
Nick,this place is insane.
是的,我知道 聽著,你是對的
Yeah,I know. Listen. You were right.
這個地方就像時鐘一般精準
This place is run like a clock.
聽著,我需要你的幫助
Listen,I need your help.
我拿到了一些密碼序列號...
I've been keeping some event sequences...
Nick,我覺得這聽上去有點奇怪
Nick,it was hard to put all this together,
但是,我認為我們生病或被感染了,你懂嗎
but,you know,I think we're sick,or infected.
嘿,Jonah,我真的覺得你不該胡思亂想
Hey,Jonah,stop thinking like that,man. Seriously.
不,他們試圖讓我感覺自己有什麼奇怪的變化
No,they're trying to keep whatever's inside us from metastasizing.
Jonah,停下
Jonah,stop.
那只是一些基本測試,懂嗎?
Nothing's metastasizing,okay?
-我們很好,我們沒事的 -不,我有事
We're fine. We're gonna be fine. No,I'm not.
-你要相信我 -我的身體有問題
Just trust me on this. No,my body is not.
我們得離開這裏
We gotta get out of here.
是啊,我知道了,我們會離開的
Yeah,I know. We will.
好吧,我拿到了小鍵盤上的按鍵數字
Okay,I've got the variables on my keypad.
我要你幫我做另一半的數字排序,好嗎?
Now I need you to take back half the sequences,okay?
-好的  -很好  -我會幫忙的
Yeah. I'll help. Okay.
不過,我的眼鏡壞了
But my glasses are messed up,though.
嘿,沒問題的
Hey,it's gonna be fine.
我們都沒問題的,別擔心你的眼鏡
It's gonna be fine. Don't worry about your glasses.
好吧,我告訴你鍵盤的樣子
Okay,I'm gonna give it to you spatially.
它就像手機上的鍵盤  好了,你準備好了嗎?
Three v three phone style. Okay,you ready?
-準備好了 -好
Yeah. Okay.
上中,中中,左上,左下
Top-middle,middle-middle,top-left,bottom-left.
2 5 1 7
2-5-1-7.
你都記下了嗎
You got it?
左下 第一
Bottom-left first.
中中第二 上中第三
Middle-middle second. Top-middle third.
左上 第四
Top-left last.
Nick,有件事讓我很困擾
Nick,I'm having a hard time handling this.
有天他們讓我喝了一些奇怪的東西
They made me drink some weird stuff the other day
然後我的手臂就沒知覺了
and I haven't really been able to feel my arms.
你的手?什麼?什​​麼意思?
Your arms? What? What do you mean?
哦,天哪
Oh,God!
-Jonah,發生什麼事了? -我得閃了
Dude,who is it? I gotta go.
Jonah,等一下
Jonah,hold on a second.
Jonah!Jonah!
Jonah! Jonah!
Jonah!
啟動
Agitate.
"趕緊出來"
Everybody outside.
女:掩護小隊,14級警報
Recovery team to level 14.
"對像"已越獄
Subject has breached.
男:"對像"在逃
Subject has escaped.
哦,對不起,我只是想找點水喝
Oh,sorry,I was just looking for the water fountain.
男:掩護小隊,14級警報
Recovery team to level 14.
"對像"已越獄,逃跑中
Subject has breached. Escaped.
你能抬起你的手臂嗎
Can you raise your arm?
走廊裏發生什麼了
What happened in the hallway?
很好
Good.
腿還是沒有感覺?
Still no feeling in your legs?
Jonah出了什麼事?
What happened to Jonah?
你看,我知道你們能聽到我和他在通風口的對話
Look,I know you guys know I can talk to him through the vent.
你們到底對他做了什麼?
What the hell did you guys do with him?
是的,Nick,我們一直在監聽
Yes,Nick,we have been listening to you,
但事實際上是......
but the truth of the matter...
事情的真相是,我像小白鼠一樣被關在這裏
The truth of the matter is,total Mickey Mouse operation here.
過時的方法,就像政府扶持的恐龍研究
Antiquated methodologies,dinosaurs with government grants.
很久之前建立了這麼一個巨大的研究設施
A whole facility built during the first wave of Big Science
過時,但他們繼續
outdated but allowed to continue
假裝這裏很重要
pretending that you're important.
-我也覺得你不值,很可悲 -Nick
I feel sorry for you. It's pathetic. Nick.
"事情的真相"
"The truth of the matter."
什麼是這事的真相?
What is the truth of the matter here?
我唯一能肯定的真相就是
The only thing I know for certain is that
你不知道你在做什麼
you don't know what you're dealing with.
你能從這個過時的、垃圾的..
You will be pulled from this shitty little shack
你所謂的研究機構裏
you call a research facility so fast
得到的唯一東西就是
that the only thing relevant to be shown for any of this
當一切都曝光的時候,你會被抹掉破,沒人會記得你
is the way it's all exposed,wrecked,and forgotten.
你沒辦法!你不知該做什麼!對吧?
You have no idea! You have no clue! Do you?
你不會知道有多少像Jonah和Nomad這樣的孩子能迅速的曝光
Have any clue how fast dumb,lost little kids like me,Jonah or Nomad
並毀掉這麼個地方
could ruin a place like this?
沒多久這裏的一切活動將被停止  人們會問這是什麼地方?
Have it come to a grinding halt like the stone wheel it is?
Damon,你身處狂野的西部,法律在這裏沒多大作用
You're clueless law in the Wild West,Damon.
沒有什麼能保得住你,你這個可悲的傢伙
You're a relic protecting ruins. You're pathetic.
事情的真相是,我是唯一一個你還能繼續在這裏待下去的理由
The truth of the matter is,I'm the only one with any sense around here.
你的朋友Jonah
Your friend Jonah
從來沒來過這裏,Nick
was never here,Nick.
我們沒能救活他
We never recovered him.
胡說
Bullshit!
我一直在通風口和他說話
I've been talking to him through the vent this whole time.
你確定?
Have you really?
通過通風口?Nick
Through your vent,Nick?
三,四,五,六,七...
Three,four,five,six,seven...
該死
Shit.
該死!
Shit!
該死的!
God damn it!
Nick
Nick.
嘿...
Hey.
感覺怎麼樣?
How are you feeling?
好些了
Better.
我做了場美夢
I had a wonderful dream.
是嗎?
Oh,Yeah?
你,嗯...
You,um...
你個...
You...
你贏了@%%￥&.....
You won your regionals.
嘿,醒醒.
Hay,wake up.
醒醒
Wake up.
Haley
Haley.
停下!放開我,放開我!
Stop it,get off of me! Get off of me!
你到底在幹嘛?放開我!Haley!
What the hell are you doing? Let go of me! Haley!
Haley,快醒醒!
Haley,wake up!
嘿,放開我!停下!你們到底TM在幹嘛?
Hey,let go of me! Stop it! What the hell do you think you're doing?
Haley,快醒醒!Haley!
Haley,wake up! Haley!
起來!
Wake up!
天哪...天哪...
Holy... Holy...
不!搞什麼鬼?
No! What the hell?
Damon!
他們把我的腿怎麼了!?
What did they do to my legs?
Nick,我們需要你冷靜下來
Nick,we are going to need you to calm down.
現在你知道我們為什麼對你那麼有興趣了
Now you understand why we've been so interested in you.
正如你所看到的,你的情況 是非常奇特的.
As you can see,your circumstances are very peculiar.
相信我,我們不想打擊你
And believe me,we didn't want to shock you with this.
我敢肯定,現在 你會感謝我們為你做的一切
I'm sure by now you can appreciate where we're coming from.
現在,為了您的安全,也為了我們的安全
Now,for your safety and ours,
我會需要你去連接到那個IV設備
I'm going to need you to hook yourself up to that IV.
就在那邊.
Right over there.
Nick
Nick.
我需要你
I need you
冷靜下來
to calm down.
Nick
Nick.
別這樣
Don't do this.
為什麼...
Why...
你為什麼不告訴關於我的腿的事
Why didn't you tell me what happened to my legs?
怎麼能告訴你
How could we?
我們那時剛讓你恢復
We had just recovered you.
現在聽我說
Now listen to me.
對你來說上面是非常危險的
It is extremely dangerous for you up there.
我只能在遠離他們的地下保護你
I can only safeguard you from them down here.
他們是誰?
Safeguard me from who?
你還好嗎?
You okay?
腿能動嗎?
Can you feel your legs?
來吧,我們走
Come on,we gotta move.
我們走
We gotta move.
你還好嗎?
You okay?
-發生了什麼?  -來吧,我們走
What's happening? Come on,let's go.
抱歉打斷你一下
I'm sorry to interrupt,
你知道還有多久到加油站嗎?
but do you know how long it is until the gas station?
嗯?
Hmm?
呵呵,沒多少路了
Oh,it's just up a ways.
好,謝謝,我們這是在哪裏?
Okay. Thank you. And where are we exactly?
我們的車拋錨了,各種迷路
When our car broke down,we kind of got lost.
沒事的
That's okay.
經常有人在這裏迷路
Tha thappens to a lot of people out in these parts.
是啊
Right.
我總是告訴人們
I always tell people
讓他們不要緊張
they should take comfort in the thought
它們總會保佑我們的
that they are always watching over us.
嗯
Hmm.
你聽到了嗎?
Did you hear that?
聽到什麼?
Hear what?
聽著,把嘴張開,像這樣
Listen,with your mouth open,like this.
你說啥?
Excuse me?
它們正看著我們呢
Their horns are watching over us.
對不起,誰在看著我們呢?
I'm sorry. Who's watching us?
上帝的小天使.
God's little angels.
還能是誰呢
Who else?
再次感謝你送我們
Thanks again for the ride.
你只要好好的休息一天
You have the rest of the day nicely.
就能從裏到外煥然一新
Just push from the inside out.
再見
Bye.
Bye. Bye.
-別忘了,煥然一新 -好的,謝謝.
Okay,thanks.
我要去打個電話,好嗎?
I'm gonna go use the phone,okay?
我會找到人幫忙的,呆在這裏
I'm gonna get us help. Stay here.
別走開
Don't move.
Haley!
Haley,坐下 坐下
Haley,sit down. Sit down.
我認真的,好嗎?
I'm serious,okay?
我認真的,別走開
I'm serious. Don't move.
我們會離開這裏,好嗎?
I'm gonna get us out of here,okay?
好的
Yeah,okay.
女:線路當前不可用
The network is currently unavailable.
請稍後再試
Please try again later.
線路當前不可用的
The network is currently unavailable.
請稍後再試.
Please try again later.
二級,是可傳染性的
The two subjects,considered possibly contagious,
從醫學研究設施中逃跑
have escaped from a medical research facility.
Nickholas Eastman 和 Haley Pedersen
Nickholas Eastman and Haley Peterson
我們認為它們是徒步跳脫,請不要接近他們
are believed to be traveling on foot and should not be approached.
地方當局友情提醒
Please alert your local authorities.
謝謝
Thank you.
現在,我們將恢復正常的節目播放
Now we'll return to your regularly scheduled programming.
Haley!
嘿!
Hey!
Haley!
-停車! -天哪
Stop the truck! Christ.
你到底在幹嘛?
What the hell are you doing?
滾開!快滾開!
Get back! You get back now!
把車停下!停車!
Stop the truck! Stop it!
-滾下我的卡車! -Haley!停車!
Get off my truck! Haley! Stop the truck!
Haley!
你給我滾下去!
Get off the goddamn truck!
-滾開! -Haley!
Get away! Haley!
-停車!  -你腦殘嗎!?
Stop! What is wrong with you?
我靠,你的腿是怎麼回事?
Boy,what's going on with your leg?
來吧
Come on.
你跑不遠的
You won't get far.
Nick
Nick.
Nick,你的腿怎麼了?
Nick,what happened to your legs?
Haley,我已經向你解釋過了
Haley,I already explained to you.
你感覺好點了嗎?
Are you feeling okay?
恩
Yeah.
是的,我沒事
Yeah,I'm okay.
我們會沒事的
We're gonna be fine.
just......只是盡量放鬆
Just... Just try to relax.
哦,該死
Oh,shit.
發生什麼事了警官?
Is something wrong,Officer?
我惹什麼麻煩了嗎?
Is there some kind of trouble?
一點也不麻煩,夫人.
No trouble at all,ma'am.
一點也不麻煩.
No trouble at all.
請
Please.
能跟我走一趟嗎?
Will you accompany me?
當然了
Certainly.
這沒道理啊...
It doesn't make any sense.
公路在哪裏?
Where's the rest of the road?
布拉斯,你最近有和陌生人接觸過嗎?
Mirabelle,have you had contact with any strangers lately?
噢,有過
Oh,yes.
我門聊了很多美好的事物
We talked about so many wonderful things.
你把他們帶去哪裏了?布拉斯?
But where did you take them,Mirabelle?
你接觸他們的目的是什麼?
What was your proximity to them?
這是很容易找到的
It is so easy to find.
總是這麼好聽 對色位 的黑夜.
Always such a nice bit of color against the dark nights.
漆黑的夜晚,黑夜.
Dark nights,dark nights.
漆黑的夜晚,漆黑的夜晚.
漆黑的夜晚,夜...
Dark nights,nights...
我們可以去野餐.
We could have a picnic.
野餐
A picnic.
Have a picnic.
在...
In a...
在一個...
On a...
我們來接你
We're coming to get you.
又碰到峽谷了?
Is that the same canyon?
我不知道,我想我們繞過峽谷了
I don't know. I thought we already passed it. Before.
也許我們繞回來了?
Maybe we circled back?
可能吧,我不知道.
Yeah,maybe. I don't know.
看起來像是廢棄了
It looks abandoned.
你在找什麼?
What are you looking for?
槍 或是手機 又或地圖之類的東西
A gun,like,a cell phone or a map or something in here.
你想穿嗎?
Do you wanna wear that?
來吧,我們去一探究竟
Come on,let's check it out.
女:線路當前不可用
The network is currently unavailable.
Haley,你有沒有發現什麼?
Haley,did you find anything?
Haley?
嘿...
Hey-
是啊,我發現了一個地圖,但是上面沒有任何信息
Yeah,I found a map,but there's not much information on it.
"你在這裏."
"You are here."
但是,這不可能啊
But we can't be.
我們往這邊開的是吧
We drove down,right?
這是不是我們剛才路過的峽谷?
Isn't that the same gorge we just came from?
然後那個小鎮,溫泉鎮,應該是這裏,對不對?
Then that town,Good Springs,should be down here,right?
可能吧
I guess.
我搞糊塗了
I don't get it.
你覺得那是什麼聲音?
What do you think that sound is?
我什麼都沒聽到,Haley.
I don't hear anything,Hay.
什麼樣的聲音?
What sound?
聽
There.
我認為應該在這兒過夜
I think we should stay here tonight.
這是我的錯嗎?
Is this my fault?
什麼?不
What? No.
如果有的話,也是我的錯
If anything,it's my fault.
我也同意了去追蹤Nomad
I was the one who wanted to follow Nomad.
我記不得了
I don't remember.
腿疼嗎?
Do they hurt?
沒事的
It's okay.
好寬
So wide.
我希望能找到過河的地方
I hope we can get across it.
Haley 嘿,嘿.
Haley, hey, hey!
我們應該進去
We should go inside.
Jonah!
Jonah!Jonah!別,Jonah!Jonah!是我!
Jonah! Jonah! No,Jonah! Jonah! It's me!
Jonah,Jonah,Jonah!嘿,是我!嘿!是我Nick
Jonah,Jonah,Jonah! Hey,it's Nick! Hey! It's Nick!
Jonah,嘿嘿  嘿  哥們,是我 是我
Jonah,hey. Hey,buddy,it's me. It's me.
該死
Shit.
你好,James
Hello,James.
好久不見.
Long time no see.
"你好,James"
"Hello,James."
我在找三個人 兩名男性 一名女性
I'm trying to locate three individuals. Two males,one female.
都極具傳染性
All extremely contagious.
你有沒有和他們接觸過?James
Have you had any contact with them,James?
你在家做什麼?
What are you doing in my house?
我很高興看到你在這裏住的很舒服,但是這是你的房子嗎?
I'm glad to see you're comfortable here,but is this your house?
這兒屬於我的媽媽.
Belongs to my mommy.
-我弟弟睡在那兒 -是嗎?
My brother sleeps right there. Yes?
-我睡在那兒,我還養了一隻小貓咪
And I sleep right there,and I have a little kitty.
你的兄弟,你的母親和你的貓咪
Your brother,your mother and your kitty.
是啊
Yeah.
你還記得他們的名字嗎,James?
Can you remember their names,James?
你非凡的的求生意志
Extraordinary,your will to survive
助長了你的憤怒,恐懼,孤獨,沮喪
fueled by your anger,your fear,loneliness,frustration.
我很佩服你
I admire you.
我不明白
I don't understand.
沒事的,James
It's all right,James.
我很抱歉 我丟下你們跑了
I'm sorry I left you guys there.
我發誓有人幫助我逃跑
You know,I swear someone was helping me,
我只是沒辦法帶你們一起跑
though I just can't bring it together.
Jonah,那個地方是...
Jonah,that place was...
那個地方!這個地方!這都是一樣的,Nick
That place! This place! It's all the same,Nick.
這都是一樣的
It's all the same.
你在說什麼呢?
What are you talking about?
看看你的腿,夥計
Look at your legs,man.
看看你的腿.看看我們
Look at your legs. Look at us.
皮膚上的數字.
Look for the numbers.
對於...那數字紋身
For... The tattoo.
你有紋身?
Do you have a tattoo?
這不是一個ID號碼?
This isn't an ID number?
它就是一個ID號,
It is an ID number,
不只是你有這個號碼
but it's just not for you.
這整個區域的人都有,Nick
It's an ID for this whole area,Nick.
2,加3,加5,加41
Two,plus three,plus five,plus 41.
51.
51區,Nick,我們在51區
Area 51,Nick. We're in Area 51.
-Jonah,我不敢確定...  -不,看看你的腿!
Jonah,I'm not sure... No,look at your legs!
我正看著它呢!
I'm looking at my legs!
看,空的
Watch. Empty.
一切都是空的,他們正在監測我們,Nick
Everything is empty. They're testing us,Nick.
我們就像小白鼠
We're like little rats.
現在,你看過地圖了嗎?
Now,did you see the maps?
你在說什麼,地圖?
What are you talking about,the maps?
你在告訴我,這些都是假的嗎?
What are you telling me,it's not real?
當然,它是真實的.
Of course it's real.
有道路,公路,和一些城鎮
There's roads,highways,cities on these maps.
它們原本不存在的
They don't exist.
我們被困在一個巨大的政府機構裏
We're trapped in a huge government annex.
-你...你有見過一個當地人嗎?  -Jonah
Did you meet any of the charming locals? Jonah.
Jonah,聽我說
Jonah,listen to me.
聽我說
Listen to me.
Haley是真的,我們真的病了
Haley is really,really sick.
我們必須告訴其他人  我們必須告訴其他人
Okay,we have to tell someone. We have to tell someone.
我們要揭露這裏
We have to expose this.
我生病了
I'm sick,too.
這很難解釋,但有什麼東西在我身上.
It's hard to explain,but there's something in me.
這就像是......這就像他們從我身上拿走了什麼,Nick
There's something that is... It's like they took something from me,Nick.
拿走了什麼?
Took what?
我覺得我...
I feel like I'm...
我覺得我全身都...
I feel like I'm full of...
-少點什麼? -是的
Gaps? Yes.
但到底少什麼
That's exactly what it is.
我的意思是,感覺不是自己的,你懂嗎?只是感覺像自己的
I mean,not exactly,but,you know,it's really close.
所以,你明白我的意思嗎?
So you know what I mean?
Jonah,這是誰的血?
Jonah,whose blood is that?
是你的嗎?
Is that yours?
我只是想把這些東西拿下來
I was trying to get them off.
嘿,哥們.
Hey,buddy.
我們要逃跑,跑去人多的地方
We're gonna get somewhere where we can be seen by
很多人越多越好,好嗎?
as many people as possible,okay?
這是唯一安全的辦法了
It's the only way to be safe.
它們拿不下來
They won't come off.
但是,我們該怎麼逃跑?
But how would we do that?
據我所知,這裏只有一條路
From what I've seen,there's only one road in here.
嗯,我們就走這條路
Well,that's the one we take.
好的,別緊張 別緊張
Okay,we're good. We're good.
就停這裏,熄火
Stop right there. Hold up.
嘿嘿,兄弟.別急,我們不趕時間
Hey,boss. We have full clearance to pass.
準備檢查,我們開始
Check it out. Let's go.
請你下車,先生.
Step out of your vehicle,sir.
不,我不必下來
No. That's okay.
就是現在了!
It's time to go!
攔住他 攔住他
Block him down. Block him down.
該死!加油
Shit! Come on!
該死!
Shit!
-我的天哪!別下車!
For God's sake,Nick! Stay in the truck!
跑,Nick!
Run,Nick!
Jonah,你在做什麼?
Jonah,what are you doing?
這..這沒法打字啊
it doesn't fucking type!
Jonah!
Jonah,來吧,我們快走!快上車!
Jonah,come on,let's go! Get in the truck!
趕快!快上車!
Come on! Get back in!
Jonah,快上車!
Jonah,get in the truck!
我不行了,我不行了
I'm done. I'm done.
只是回車上去
Just get in the truck.
Nick 別放棄
Nick,keep up.
上車去
Get in the truck.
你踩死拿該死的油門,當我跟你說走的時候
You put this shit on the accelerator,go when I yell,"Go."
你立刻跑
You go,Nick.
好嗎 Nick?
Okay,Nick?
你必須走
I need you to go.
你必須走,求你了
I need you to go. Please.
扣上你的安全帶
Put your seatbelt on.
-Nick,我覺得我們..... -堅持住
-Nick,I think we should just... -Hold on.
Nick,停車!
Nick,stop!
對不起
I'm sorry.
我愛你
I love you.
Haley!
想都別想,Nick
Don't even think about it,Nick.
你救不了她的
You can't reach her.
在我這邊
On my side.
看看你自己,Nick
Take a look at yourself,Nick.
人類的意識與外星科技
The perfect integration of human will
的完美融合
and alien technology.
我們最成功的作品
Our finest achievement.
Nomad?
Nomad!
Nomad,就是我,我引你們來的這裏
Nomad,yes. I brought you here.
但要記住,Nick,是你自己主動想來抓我的
But remember,Nick,you were the one who came looking for me.
所以,你可能要問自己,
So you might want to ask yourself,
"我究竟有沒有找到想要的東西?"
"Did I find what I was looking for?"